<resources>
    <string name="app_name">10 Days of Good Habits</string>
    <string name="day_one">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day_two">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day_three">Day 3</string>
    <string name="day_four">Day 4</string>
    <string name="day_five">Day 5</string>
    <string name="day_six">Day 6</string>
    <string name="day_seven">Day 7</string>
    <string name="day_eight">Day 8</string>
    <string name="day_nine">Day 9</string>
    <string name="day_ten">Day 10</string>
    <string name="top_description_one">Drink an average of 3 liters of water per day</string>
    <string name="top_description_two">Work out at the gym at least 3 times per week</string>
    <string name="top_description_three">Take cold showers every day</string>
    <string name="top_description_four">Reduce your sugar intake</string>
    <string name="top_description_five">Read books</string>
    <string name="top_description_six">Eat healthy foods</string>
    <string name="top_description_seven">Sleep on the side or back</string>
    <string name="top_description_eight">Brush your teeth twice a day</string>
    <string name="top_description_nine">Sleep 8 hours a day</string>
    <string name="top_description_ten">Have a skincare routine</string>
    <string name="bottom_description_one">Water is vital to our health. It plays a key role in many of our body\'s functions,
        including bringing nutrients to cells, getting rid of wastes, protecting joints and organs, and maintaining body
        temperature.</string>
    <string name="bottom_description_two">Going to the gym can improve your brain health, help manage weight, reduce the risk
        of disease, strengthen bones and muscles, and improve your ability to do everyday activities.</string>
    <string name="bottom_description_three">The benefits of cold showers include boosting the immune system, combating symptoms
        of depression, improving blood circulation, and reducing inflammation and swelling.</string>
    <string name="bottom_description_four">Reducing your sugar intake may support a healthy weight, decrease your risk of
        depression, and reduce your risk of heart disease, among other health benefits.</string>
    <string name="bottom_description_five">Reading improves your focus, memory, empathy, and communication skills.
        It can reduce stress, improve your mental health, and help you live longer.</string>
    <string name="bottom_description_six">Eating healthy foods is essential for maintaining overall health and well-being. Aim
        to incorporate a diverse range of fruits, vegetables, whole grains, lean proteins, and healthy fats into your meals and
        snacks.</string>
    <string name="bottom_description_seven">sleeping on the side or back is considered more beneficial than sleeping on the
        stomach. In either of these sleep positions, it\'s easier to keep your spine supported and balanced, which relieves
        pressure on the spine and enables your muscles to relax and recover.</string>
    <string name="bottom_description_eight">It\'s important to maintain good oral hygiene by brushing your teeth at least twice
        a day, ideally in the morning and before bed. This routine helps remove plaque and prevents tooth decay and gum disease.
        Using fluoride toothpaste and a soft-bristled toothbrush can help keep your teeth and gums healthy. </string>
    <string name="bottom_description_nine">Adequate sleep is crucial for overall health and well-being. It supports physical
        health by promoting immune function, reducing the risk of chronic diseases, and regulating weight. In terms of mental
        health, sleep aids emotional regulation, enhances cognitive function, and stabilizes mood. </string>
    <string name="bottom_description_ten">Having a skincare routine is essential for maintaining healthy, radiant skin and
        preventing skin issues and environmental damage.</string>
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">See more or less information about the habit.</string>
</resources>